<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<NOTICES>
<PRESOL>
<DATE>09212013</DATE>
<AGENCY><![CDATA[Department of Veterans Affairs]]></AGENCY>
<OFFICE><![CDATA[VA Caribbean Health Care System]]></OFFICE>
<LOCATION><![CDATA[Department of Veterans Affairs Caribbean Health Care System]]></LOCATION>
<ZIP>22182</ZIP>
<CLASSCOD>65</CLASSCOD>
<OFFADD><![CDATA[2500 Lakemont Ave., Orlando, FL 32803]]></OFFADD>
<SUBJECT><![CDATA[65--MULTILAB SERIES VASCULAR SYSTEM]]></SUBJECT>
<SOLNBR><![CDATA[VA248-13-Q-3162]]></SOLNBR>
<RESPDATE>09252013</RESPDATE>
<ARCHDATE>03242014</ARCHDATE>
<CONTACT><![CDATA[Name: Victoria Robles, Title: Contract Specialist, Phone: 4076464314, Fax: 7877818721, Email: victoria.robles@va.gov;]]></CONTACT>
<DESC><![CDATA[Bids are being solicited under solicitation number VA248-13-Q-3162.  This announcement constitutes the only solicitation; bids are being requested and a written solicitation will not be issued. The solicitation is issued as an invitation for bids (IFB), unless otherwise indicated herein.If your company can provide the product/services listed on the solicitation and comply with all of the solicitation instructions, please respond to this notice. To view the specifications, please go to www.FedBid.com and reference Buy No. 566036.<BR> <BR>GSA Schedule Bids Only:  Sellers bidding on this opportunity MUST have the items requested on an existing GSA Schedule. The Schedule must either be in the Seller's name or the Seller must be able to document its ability to act as an agent of a partner's Schedule. Sellers must not bid more than their applicable contract ceiling price, excluding the FedBid Fee, for contract-specific items. If FedBid receives notice that, due to inclusion of the FedBid Fee, the Selected Bid's line item pricing is higher than the Selected Seller's applicable published government contract pricing, the FedBid Fee will be reduced to ensure the Selected Bid's line item pricing does not exceed the Selected Seller's applicable contract pricing. Sellers may offer Open Market items only in accordance with the approved Terms and Conditions of their respective GSA Schedule AND upon approval from the soliciting Contracting Officer. Information regarding GSA Schedules can be found at www.GSA.gov. <BR> <BR>This requirement is a [ Small Business ] set-aside and only qualified sellers may submit bids.The solicitation pricing on www.FedBid.com will start on the date this solicitation is posted and will end on 2013-09-25 14:30:00.0 Eastern Time or as otherwise displayed at www.FedBid.com.FOB Destination shall be Orlando, FL 32803 <BR> <BR>The VHA NCO 08 - 672 - San Juan, PR requires the following items, Exact Match Only, to the following:  <BR><span class="label">LI 001: </span>Multilab series 2 LHS-TI Vascular System, 1, EA; <BR><span class="label">LI 002: </span>True dicom 3 networking package, 1, EA; <BR><span class="label">LI 003: </span>Operator and maintenance manuals, 1, EA; <BR> <BR><a href="https://marketplace.fedbid.com/fbweb/fbobuyDetails.do?token=%3D%3DwBKxmaVGYR9qX%2BON23ds1NQAAAAAHeAAgAgTFCGg%2FFzzqQbJAAyVXBA0Or">Solicitation and Buy Attachments </a> <BR> <BR>***Question Submission: Interested offerors must submit any questions concerning the solicitation at the earliest time possible to enable the Buyer to respond. Questions must be submitted by using the 'Submit a Question' feature at www.fedbid.com. Questions not received within a reasonable time prior to close of the solicitation may not be considered.*** <BR> <BR>For this solicitation, VHA NCO 08 - 672 - San Juan, PR intends to conduct an online competitive reverse auction to be facilitated by the third-party reverse auction provider, FedBid, Inc. FedBid has developed an online, anonymous, browser based application to conduct the reverse auction. A Seller may submit a series of pricing bids, which descend in price during the specified period of time for the aforementioned reverse auction. VHA NCO 08 - 672 - San Juan, PR is taking this action in an effort to improve both seller access and awareness of requests and the agency's ability to gather multiple, completed, real-time bids.All responsible Sellers that respond to this solicitation MUST submit the pricing portion of their bid using the online exchange located at www.FedBid.com. There is no cost to register, review procurement data or make a bid on www.FedBid.com.Sellers that are not currently registered to use www.FedBid.com should proceed to www.FedBid.com to complete their free registration. Sellers that require special considerations or assistance may contact the FedBid Helpdesk at 877-9FEDBID (877-933-3243) or via email at clientservices@fedbid.com. Sellers may not artificially manipulate the price of a transaction on www.FedBid.com by any means. It is unacceptable to place bad faith bids, to use decoys in the www.FedBid.com process or to collude with the intent or effect of hampering the competitive www.FedBid.com process.Should Sellers require additional clarification, contact FedBid at 877-9FEDBID (877-933-3243) or clientservices@fedbid.com. <BR> <BR>Use of FedBid:   Buyers and Sellers agree to conduct this transaction through FedBid in compliance with the FedBid Terms of Use. Failure to comply with the below terms and conditions may result in offer being determined as non-responsive. <BR> <BR>In addition to any VHA buy terms entered in FedBid, the Seller (Bidder) has reviewed and acknowledges any attached solicitation documents, item details, delivery schedule, and/or instructions to Seller (collectively referred to as requirements), and agrees to all terms and conditions set forth in the solicitation documents. While additional support documentation (e.g. Seller Attachments) may be requested, pricing shall be entered as a 'bid' in the reverse auction - offline pricing is not an acceptable bid. At the conclusion of the reverse auction, if attached to the buy, the apparent winning bidder shall be required to complete the solicitation documents prior to award. <BR> <BR>New equipment ONLY, NO remanufactured products <BR> <BR>Bid MUST be good for 30 calendar days after submission <BR> <BR>FOB Destination CONUS (CONtinental U.S.) <BR> <BR>No partial shipments unless otherwise specified <BR> <BR>Agencies require registration with the Central Contractor Registry (CCR).  Information can be found at www.sam.gov <BR> <BR>small business <BR> <BR>]]></DESC>
<LINK><![CDATA[https://www.fbo.gov/spg/VA/SJVAMC672/SJVAMC672/VA248-13-Q-3162/listing.html]]></LINK>
<SETASIDE>Total Small Business</SETASIDE>
<POPCOUNTRY><![CDATA[US]]></POPCOUNTRY>
<POPZIP>32803</POPZIP>
<POPADDRESS><![CDATA[Orlando, FL 32803]]></POPADDRESS>
<RECOVERY_ACT>N</RECOVERY_ACT>
<DOCUMENT_PACKAGES/>
</PRESOL>

<COMBINE>
<DATE>08282013</DATE>
<AGENCY><![CDATA[Department of Veterans Affairs]]></AGENCY>
<OFFICE><![CDATA[Atlanta VAMC]]></OFFICE>
<LOCATION><![CDATA[Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center]]></LOCATION>
<ZIP>22182</ZIP>
<CLASSCOD>41</CLASSCOD>
<OFFADD><![CDATA[1670 Clairmont Road, Decatur, GA 30033]]></OFFADD>
<SUBJECT><![CDATA[41--Refrigerators]]></SUBJECT>
<SOLNBR><![CDATA[VA247-13-Q-1499]]></SOLNBR>
<RESPDATE>09032013</RESPDATE>
<ARCHDATE>03022014</ARCHDATE>
<CONTACT><![CDATA[Name: Quentin Deloney, Title: Contract Specialists, Phone: 4043216111, Fax: 4047287758, Email: quentin.deloney@va.gov;]]></CONTACT>
<DESC><![CDATA[This is a combined synopsis/solicitation for commercial items prepared in accordance with the format in FAR Subpart 12.6, as supplemented with additional information included in this notice.The solicitation number is VA247-13-Q-1499 and is issued as an invitation for bids (IFB), unless otherwise indicated herein.The solicitation document and incorporated provisions and clauses are those in effect through Federal Acquisition Circular FAC 2005-69. The associated North American Industrial Classification System (NAICS) code for this procurement is 335222 with a small business size standard of 1,000.00 employees.This requirement is a [ Small Business ] set-aside and only qualified offerors may submit bids.The solicitation pricing on www.FedBid.com will start on the date this solicitation is posted and will end on 2013-09-03 12:00:00.0 Eastern Time or as otherwise displayed at www.FedBid.com.FOB Destination shall be Decatur, GA 30033 <BR> <BR>The VHA NCO 07 - 508 - Atlanta, GA requires the following items, Brand Name or Equal, to the following:  <BR><span class="label">LI 001: </span>2.9 cubic foot medical refrigerator 2 door under counter refrigator with two side mounted locks.  It comes in white with hospital grade cords and 2 nist traceable thermometers with alarms also comes with a zero degree freezer (f) for vaccines which has a manual defrost, and the refrigerator section has automatic defrost with an internal air circulation fan, 31, EA; <BR> <BR><a href="https://marketplace.fedbid.com/fbweb/fbobuyDetails.do?token=%3D%3DwBKxmaVGYR9mNi%2BjqkK6YUQAAAAAHeAAgAgTFCGg%2FFzzqQbJAAyVXBA0Or">Solicitation and Buy Attachments </a> <BR> <BR>***Question Submission: Interested offerors must submit any questions concerning the solicitation at the earliest time possible to enable the Buyer to respond. Questions must be submitted by using the 'Submit a Question' feature at www.fedbid.com. Questions not received within a reasonable time prior to close of the solicitation may not be considered.*** <BR> <BR>For this solicitation, VHA NCO 07 - 508 - Atlanta, GA intends to conduct an online competitive reverse auction to be facilitated by the third-party reverse auction provider, FedBid, Inc. FedBid has developed an online, anonymous, browser based application to conduct the reverse auction. An Offeror may submit a series of pricing bids, which descend in price during the specified period of time for the aforementioned reverse auction. VHA NCO 07 - 508 - Atlanta, GA is taking this action in an effort to improve both vendor access and awareness of requests and the agency's ability to gather multiple, competed, real-time bids.All responsible Offerors that respond to this solicitation MUST submit the pricing portion of their bid using the online exchange located at www.FedBid.com. There is no cost to register, review procurement data or make a bid on www.FedBid.com.Offerors that are not currently registered to use www.FedBid.com should proceed to www.FedBid.com to complete their free registration. Offerors that require special considerations or assistance may contact the FedBid Helpdesk at 877-9FEDBID (877-933-3243) or via email at clientservices@fedbid.com. Offerors may not artificially manipulate the price of a transaction on www.FedBid.com by any means. It is unacceptable to place bad faith bids, to use decoys in the www.FedBid.com process or to collude with the intent or effect of hampering the competitive www.FedBid.com process.Should offerors require additional clarification, notify the point of contact or FedBid at 877-9FEDBID (877-933-3243) or clientservices@fedbid.com.Use of FedBid:   Buyers and Sellers agree to conduct this transaction through FedBid in compliance with the FedBid Terms of Use. Failure to comply with the below terms and conditions may result in offer being determined as non-responsive. <BR> <BR>New Equipment ONLY; NO remanufactured or "gray market" items. All items must be covered by the manufacturer's warranty. <BR> <BR>Bid MUST be good for 90 calendar days after close of Buy. <BR> <BR>This solicitation requires registration with the System for Award Management (SAM) prior to award, pursuant to applicable regulations and guidelines.  Registration information can be found at www.sam.gov. <BR> <BR>The selected Offeror must comply with the following commercial item terms and conditions, which are incorporated herein by reference: FAR 52.212-1, Instructions to Offerors - Commercial Items, applies to this acquisition; FAR 52.212-3, Offeror Representations and Certifications - Commercial Items - the selected offeror must submit a completed copy of the listed representations and certifications; FAR 52.212-4, Contract Terms and Conditions - Commercial Items; FAR 52.212-5, Contract Terms and Conditions Required To Implement Statutes or Executive Orders-Commercial Items, paragraph (a) and the following clauses in paragraph (b): 52.222-21, 52.222-26, 52.222-35, 52.222-36, 52.222-37, 52.225-13, 52.232-34. The full text of the referenced FAR clauses may be accessed electronically at https://www.acquisition.gov/far/. <BR> <BR>In addition to any VHA buy terms entered in FedBid, the Seller (Bidder) has reviewed and acknowledges any attached solicitation documents, item details, delivery schedule, and/or instructions to Seller (collectively referred to as requirements), and agrees to all terms and conditions set forth in the solicitation documents. While additional support documentation (e.g. Seller Attachments) may be requested, pricing shall be entered as a 'bid' in the reverse auction - offline pricing is not an acceptable bid. At the conclusion of the reverse auction, if attached to the buy, the apparent winning bidder shall be required to complete the solicitation documents prior to award. <BR> <BR>]]></DESC>
<LINK><![CDATA[https://www.fbo.gov/spg/VA/AtlVAMC/VAMCCO80220/VA247-13-Q-1499/listing.html]]></LINK>
<SETASIDE>Total Small Business</SETASIDE>
<POPCOUNTRY><![CDATA[US]]></POPCOUNTRY>
<POPZIP>30033</POPZIP>
<POPADDRESS><![CDATA[Decatur, GA 30033]]></POPADDRESS>
<RECOVERY_ACT>N</RECOVERY_ACT>
<DOCUMENT_PACKAGES/>
<CHANGES>
<AWARD>
<DATE>09212013</DATE>
<AGENCY><![CDATA[Department of Veterans Affairs]]></AGENCY>
<OFFICE><![CDATA[Atlanta VAMC]]></OFFICE>
<LOCATION><![CDATA[Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center]]></LOCATION>
<ZIP>22182</ZIP>
<CLASSCOD>41</CLASSCOD>
<OFFADD><![CDATA[1670 Clairmont Road, Decatur, GA 30033]]></OFFADD>
<SUBJECT><![CDATA[41--Refrigerators]]></SUBJECT>
<SOLNBR><![CDATA[VA247-13-Q-1499]]></SOLNBR>
<CONTACT><![CDATA[Name: Quentin Deloney, Title: Contract Specialists, Phone: 4043216111, Fax: 4047287758, Email: quentin.deloney@va.gov;]]></CONTACT>
<AWDNBR><![CDATA[508-3A5082]]></AWDNBR>
<AWDAMT><![CDATA[$25,202.69]]></AWDAMT>
<AWDDATE>09212013</AWDDATE>
<LINENBR><![CDATA[ALL]]></LINENBR>
<ARCHDATE>03022014</ARCHDATE>
<AWARDEE><![CDATA[ALLIED CONTRACT, INC. [DUNS: 835887738],124 N. PEORIA AVE.,TULSA OK 74120]]></AWARDEE>
<DESC><![CDATA[No Description Provided]]></DESC>
<LINK><![CDATA[https://www.fbo.gov/spg/VA/AtlVAMC/VAMCCO80220/VA247-13-Q-1499/listing.html]]></LINK>
<RECOVERY_ACT>N</RECOVERY_ACT>
<DOCUMENT_PACKAGES/>
</AWARD>

</CHANGES>
</COMBINE>


<JA>
<DATE>09182013</DATE>
<AGENCY><![CDATA[Defense Logistics Agency]]></AGENCY>
<OFFICE><![CDATA[DLA Acquisition Locations]]></OFFICE>
<LOCATION><![CDATA[DLA Aviation - BSM]]></LOCATION>
<ZIP>23297-5000</ZIP>
<CLASSCOD>61</CLASSCOD>
<NAICS>334419</NAICS>
<OFFADD><![CDATA[8000 Jefferson Davis Highway Richmond VA 23297-5000]]></OFFADD>
<SUBJECT><![CDATA[Revised J&A]]></SUBJECT>
<SOLNBR><![CDATA[SPE4A613R0433]]></SOLNBR>
<CONTACT><![CDATA[Antonio Torres Castellon, acquisition specialist, Phone 8042795473, Email antonio.torrescastellon@dla.mil - THERESA RICHARDSON, Contracting Officer, Phone 804-279-2612, Fax 804-279-2420, Email THERESA.RICHARDSON@DAL.MIL]]></CONTACT>
<STAUTH>FAR 6.302-1(c)</STAUTH>
<AWDNBR><![CDATA[SPE4A613C0234]]></AWDNBR>
<AWDDATE>09112013</AWDDATE>
<DESC><![CDATA[]]></DESC>
<LINK><![CDATA[https://www.fbo.gov/spg/DLA/J3/DSCR-BSM/SPE4A613R0433/listing.html]]></LINK>
<RECOVERY_ACT>N</RECOVERY_ACT>
<DOCUMENT_PACKAGES><PACKAGE><![CDATA[J&A]]></PACKAGE>
</DOCUMENT_PACKAGES>
</JA>

<SNOTE>
<DATE>09182013</DATE>
<AGENCY><![CDATA[U.S. Government Accountability Office]]></AGENCY>
<OFFICE><![CDATA[Acquisition Sourcing Management]]></OFFICE>
<LOCATION><![CDATA[Acquisition Management]]></LOCATION>
<ZIP>20548</ZIP>
<CLASSCOD>99</CLASSCOD>
<NAICS>511120</NAICS>
<OFFADD><![CDATA[441 G Street, NW Washington DC 20548]]></OFFADD>
<SUBJECT><![CDATA[Online Subscription Taxbase and Tax Notes]]></SUBJECT>
<SOLNBR><![CDATA[GAO-13-PO-0075]]></SOLNBR>
<RESPDATE>09272013</RESPDATE>
<CONTACT><![CDATA[Ester Saunders, Procurement Assistant, Phone 202-512-4435, Fax 202-512-3999, Email saundersE@gao.gov - Brian K. Umstead, Procurement Specialist, Phone 2025125567, Email umsteadb@gao.gov]]></CONTACT>
<DESC><![CDATA[&nbsp;<p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 14pt">SPECIALIZED DATABASE: The United States Government Accountability Office (GAO) intends to </span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 14pt; mso-bidi-font-family: Tahoma">award a sole-source purchase order to Tax Analysts, 400 S. Maple Ave., suite 400, Falls Church, VA 22046 for an </span><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 14pt">Online subscription for 50 users to Taxbase and one subscription to Tax Notes.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Period of Performance is September 30, 2013 - December 31, 2014 (a 15 month subscription). Taxbase and Tax Notes provides daily current awareness on issues related to federal tax law, regulations, and policy developments with in depth news and commentary.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Electronic archives go back to 1987.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Taxbase also includes news and analysis of current state and multi-state taxation issues online with archives going back to 1987.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>This proprietary information with original content by experts in the field of tax is only available through Tax Analysts.</span></p><p><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 14pt">&nbsp;</span></p><p style="mso-layout-grid-align: none"><span style="FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri', 'sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 14pt; mso-bidi-font-family: Tahoma">This is not a request for a quotation.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>No contract will be awarded on the basis of offers received in response to this notice.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>All inquiries and concerns must be addressed in writing to U.S. Government Accountability Office, Acquisition Management - Room 7116-7, 441 G Street, NW Washington, D.C. Attention Ester Saunders.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Responses to this notice must be received by September 27, 2013.<span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp; </span>Ester L. Saunders, Procurement Contact, voicemail (202) 512-4435, fax (202) 512-3999 email address <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span><a href="mailto:saundersE@gao.gov">saundersE@gao.gov</a> .</span></p>]]></DESC>
<LINK><![CDATA[https://www.fbo.gov/spg/GAO/GAOAM/GAOAM1/GAO-13-PO-0075/listing.html]]></LINK>
<SETASIDE>N/A</SETASIDE>
<POPCOUNTRY><![CDATA[US]]></POPCOUNTRY>
<POPZIP>20548</POPZIP>
<POPADDRESS><![CDATA[US GAO441 G ST. NWRoom 6231Washington, DC]]></POPADDRESS>
<RECOVERY_ACT>N</RECOVERY_ACT>
<DOCUMENT_PACKAGES/>
</SNOTE>
<MOD>
<DATE>05282013</DATE>
<AGENCY><![CDATA[General Services Administration]]></AGENCY>
<OFFICE><![CDATA[Public Buildings Service (PBS)]]></OFFICE>
<LOCATION><![CDATA[Property Disposal Division (9PZ)]]></LOCATION>
<ZIP>94102-3434</ZIP>
<CLASSCOD>X</CLASSCOD>
<NAICS>531120</NAICS>
<OFFADD><![CDATA[450 Golden Gate Avenue, Fourth Floor East San Francisco CA 94102-3434]]></OFFADD>
<SUBJECT><![CDATA[Request for Proposals - Rehabilitation and Adaptive Reuse of Hangar One and Management of Moffett Federal Airfield - NASA Ames Research Center - Mountain View, CA ]]></SUBJECT>
<SOLNBR><![CDATA[9PZ-HANGAR1_MFA-CA00026]]></SOLNBR>
<RESPDATE>09302013</RESPDATE>
<CONTACT><![CDATA[David Haase, Project Manager/Branch Chief, Fax 415-522-3213, Email hangar1@gsa.gov - Monica Pech, Senior Realty Specialist, Email hangar1@gsa.gov]]></CONTACT>
<DESC><![CDATA[]]></DESC>
<LINK><![CDATA[https://www.fbo.gov/spg/GSA/PBS/SanFranciscoCA/9PZ-HANGAR1_MFA-CA00026/listing.html]]></LINK>
<SETASIDE>N/A</SETASIDE>
<POPCOUNTRY><![CDATA[US]]></POPCOUNTRY>
<POPADDRESS><![CDATA[NASA Ames Research CenterMountain View, CA]]></POPADDRESS>
<RECOVERY_ACT>N</RECOVERY_ACT>
<DOCUMENT_PACKAGES/>
</MOD>

</NOTICES>